CHRISTOPHER NATIVIDAD

Somerset, NJ 08873 (732) 598-4240 - cnatividad194@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/cnatividad3/ https://github.com/cnatividad3

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal-oriented developer with a keen eye for well structured design from project inception through implementation. Experience involves contributing to highly collaborative work environments, finding solutions and ensuring customer satisfaction. Demonstrated best practices using languages such as HTML, CSS, Javascript, and SQL. Designed and coded web applications across multiple APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, SQL
- JQuery, REST API, Microsoft Office
- GitHub, Git, Visual Studio Code
- Wix Corvid Certified, Wordpress, Shopify
- Technical Support, Troubleshooting

WORK HISTORY

06/2019 to Current

Freelance Web Developer

Brandswaggin – Somerset, NJ - New Jersey

- Develop concepts, target audience, requirements, deadlines and budgets.
- Plan site by clarifying goals and designing functionality.
- Use of content management systems such as Wordpress, Wix, and Shopify.

08/2019 to 04/2020

Junior Software Engineer

Yorktel – Eatontown, NJ

- Worked closely with information management team to explore capabilities and limitations of IFS Applications 10 compared to previous IFS versions.
- Gathered and defined project requirements to deliver quality solutions such as a serial matching report utility and defective part tool.
- Responded promptly to support tickets regarding account issues, bugs/errors, system corrections, and report requests.
- Identified issues within databases, troubleshooting, and implemented effective solutions using Java, Spring, and PL/SQL.

04/2019 to 08/2019

Information Management Intern

Yorktel - Eatontown, NJ

- Reported to Chief Information Officer on a weekly basis to provide detailed project reports and milestone updates.
- Configured and tested FastAP software used for invoice scanning and recognition.
- Constructed instructional documentation and videos for team members on new software usage.

EDUCATION

2018

Certificate In Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Rutgers, The State University Of New Jersey - New Brunswick, NJ

05/2017

Bachelor of Science: Exercise Science and Sport Studies, Applied Kinesiology Option

Rutgers University School of Arts And Sciences - New Brunswick, NJ